[
  {
    "id": "202",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What about the design of S3 gives it it's 11 9s durability and 4 9s availability?",
      "answers": [
        "Your S3 data is spread across multiple devices and facilities",
        "Amazon links its data centers with high speed connections",
        "S3 is completely stored on solid state devices",
        "S3 is built on RAID devices"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Your S3 data is spread across multiple devices and facilities"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "203",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "How are S3 names unique across the AWS infrastructure?",
      "answers": [
        "S3 is a universal namespace; names must be unique globally",
        "S3 allows you complete freedom in naming your objects",
        "S3 uses IAM policies to make your namespace unique",
        "S3 uses proprietary name creation logic to make your names unique"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3 is a universal namespace; names must be unique globally"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "204",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "What are the elements of the S3 url pattern: s3-_____.amazonaws.com/_______?",
      "answers": [
        "region name, as in us-east-2",
        "bucket name, as in acloudguru",
        "account name, as in administrator",
        "access key id"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["region name, as in us-east-2", "bucket name, as in acloudguru"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "205",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you upload a file to S3 you will receive an HTTP return code of what if the upload was successful?",
      "answers": [
        "200",
        "400",
        "500",
        "202"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["200"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "206",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "Concerning the S3 data consistency model, which of the following are true?",
      "answers": [
        "Read after write consistency for PUTS of new objects",
        "Eventual consistency for overwrite PUTS and DELETES (can take some time to propagate)",
        "Updates are atomic: you either get the new object or you get the unaltered old object",
        "Read and write are consistent instantaneously",
        "Immediate consistency for overwrite PUTS and DELETES (propagate immediately)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Read after write consistency for PUTS of new objects", "Eventual consistency for overwrite PUTS and DELETES (can take some time to propagate)", "Updates are atomic: you either get the new object or you get the unaltered old object"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "207",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 5",
      "question": "S3 objects consist of the following?",
      "answers": [
        "Key (the name of the object)",
        "Value (the data which is made up of a sequence of bytes)",
        "Version ID (important for versioning)",
        "Metadata (data about the data you are storing)",
        "Subresources (ACL - access control lists, torrent - the bit torrent protocol)",
        "Access Key ID (the ID used to store the object)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Key (the name of the object)", "Value (the data which is made up of a sequence of bytes)", "Version ID (important for versioning)", "Metadata (data about the data you are storing)", "Subresources (ACL - access control lists, torrent - the bit torrent protocol)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "208",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "To make sure objects are not bunched together in storage based on their name, like in log file names, what should you do to make sure the objects are stored evenly?",
      "answers": [
        "Add a 'salt' to the beginning of the file name",
        "Add a 'salt' to the end of the file name",
        "Use the S3 API to spread the files across storage",
        "Use an algorithm to spread the files across storage"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Add a 'salt' to the beginning of the file name"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "209",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What level of availability is S3 designed for?",
      "answers": [
        "99.99%",
        "99.9%",
        "99.999999999% - 11 9s",
        "99.999%"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["99.99%"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "210",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What level of durability is S3 designed for?",
      "answers": [
        "99.99%",
        "99.9%",
        "99.999999999% - 11 9s",
        "99.999%"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["99.999999999% - 11 9s"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "211",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "What are the techniques used to secure your S3 buckets?",
      "answers": [
        "Access Control Lists",
        "Bucket Policies",
        "Network Access Control List Groups",
        "Security Groups",
        "Bastion Hosts"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Access Control Lists", "Bucket Policies"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "212",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "S3 has tiered availability?",
      "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["True"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "213",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "S3 has Life cycle management?",
      "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["True"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "214",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "S3 does NOT support versioning?",
      "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["False"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "215",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "S3 does NOT support encryption?",
      "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["False"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "216",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "The S3 service is designed to sustain the loss of _____ facilities concurrently?",
      "answers": [
        "2",
        "1",
        "3",
        "4"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["2"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "217",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which tier of S3 service is for data that is accessed less frequently, but requires rapid access when needed?",
      "answers": [
        "S3-IA",
        "S3",
        "Reduced Redundancy Storage (RRS)",
        "Glacier"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3-IA"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "218",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which tier of S3 service is less expensive than S3 but you are charged a retrieval fee when you access objects stored at this tier?",
      "answers": [
        "S3-IA",
        "S3",
        "Reduced Redundancy Storage (RRS)",
        "Glacier"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3-IA"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "219",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which tier of S3 service is designed for 99.99% durability and 99.99% availability of objects over a given year?",
      "answers": [
        "S3-IA",
        "S3",
        "Reduced Redundancy Storage (RRS)",
        "Glacier"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Reduced Redundancy Storage (RRS)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "220",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which tier of S3 service is less expensive and is used for data you can regenerate, like thumb nails of images?",
      "answers": [
        "S3-IA",
        "S3",
        "Reduced Redundancy Storage (RRS)",
        "Glacier"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Reduced Redundancy Storage (RRS)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "221",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which tier of S3 service is very inexpensive but used for archival only (it takes 3 to 5 hours to restore form this tier of S3 service)?",
      "answers": [
        "S3-IA",
        "S3",
        "Reduced Redundancy Storage (RRS)",
        "Glacier"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glacier"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "222",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "On S3 you are charged for which of the following?",
      "answers": [
        "Storage",
        "Requests (number of requests)",
        "Data Transfer Out",
        "Transfer Acceleration",
        "Data Transfer In"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Storage", "Requests (number of requests)", "Data Transfer Out", "Transfer Acceleration"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "223",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "How do you configure S3 to allow for allocation of costs by department or group?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Storage Management Pricing - using tags to identify groups or departments",
        "Use IAM groups",
        "Use IAM roles",
        "Use IAM users"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Storage Management Pricing - using tags to identify groups or departments"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "224",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Is S3 block based or object based storage?",
      "answers": [
        "Object based storage",
        "Block based storage",
        "Neither"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Object based storage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "225",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You should use S3 to install an OS or a database?",
      "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["False"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "226",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "S3 files can be withing which range in size?",
      "answers": [
        "0 to 5TB",
        "0 to 5GB",
        "0 to 10TB",
        "0 to 100GB"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["0 to 5TB"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "227",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "S3s file storage limit is which?",
      "answers": [
        "5TB",
        "100TB",
        "Unlimited",
        "100PB"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Unlimited"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "228",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What type of namespace does S3 use?",
      "answers": [
        "universal/global",
        "local",
        "user defined",
        "regional"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["universal/global"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "229",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In S3 bucket and file names must be _______?",
      "answers": [
        "unique globally",
        "unique locally",
        "unique regionally",
        "ubiquitous"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["unique globally"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "230",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In S3 bucket and file names must be _______?",
      "answers": [
        "unique globally",
        "unique locally",
        "unique regionally",
        "ubiquitous"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["unique globally"]
    }
  }
]
